/*quiz_data1 */

const questions = [
    {
//33問目
question:"all(決定詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["走る","全て","終わり","もっとも"],
correctAnswer: "全て"
    },
    {
//53問目
question:"some(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["誰","いくらか","好む","悪い"],
correctAnswer: "いくらか"

    },
    {
//75問目
question:"look(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["女性","～で","決して～しない","見る"],
correctAnswer: "見る"
    },
    {
//91問目
question:"much(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["手に持つ","本","場所","たくさん"],
correctAnswer: "たくさん"
    },
    {
//116問目
question:"between(前置詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["終わり","女性","名前","～の間"],
correctAnswer: "～の間"
    },
    {
//124問目
question:"great(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["平らな、等しい","秒","実際","巨大な、多量の"],
correctAnswer: "巨大な、多量の"
    },
    {
//136問目
question:"start(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["話す","始める","見解","年齢"],
correctAnswer: "始める"
    },
    {
//167問目
question:"group(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["車","部品","集団","生命"],
correctAnswer: "集団"
    },
    {
//174問目
question:"let(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["全て","働く","させる","理解する"],
correctAnswer: "させる"
    },
    {
//183問目
question:"always(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["いつも","はい","まで","～するつもりだ"],
correctAnswer: "いつも"
    }
];

export default questions;

